goalsarena.tv 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy

**Goals Arena Privacy Policy**

Our Company is part of the Our Company Group which includes Our Company International  
and Our Company Direct. This privacy policy will explain how our organization uses the  
personal data we collect from you when you use our website.

 **Topics:**  
• What data do we collect?  
• How do we collect your data?  
• How will we use your data?  
• How do we store your data?  
• Marketing  
• What are your data protection rights?  
• What are cookies?  
• How do we use cookies?  
• What types of cookies do we use?  
• How to manage your cookies  
• Privacy policies of other websites  
• Changes to our privacy policy  
• How to contact us  
• How to contact the appropriate authorities  
What data do we collect?  
Our Company collects the following data:  
• Personal identification information (Name, email address, phone number, etc.)

 **How do we collect your data?**  
You directly provide Our Company with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process  
data when you:  
• Register online or place an order for any of our products or services.  
• Voluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback on any of our message  
boards or via email.  
• Use or view our website via your browser's cookies.  
Our Company may also receive your data indirectly from the following sources:

 **How will we use your data?**  
Our Company collects your data so that we can:  
• Process your order, manage your account.  
• Email you with special offers on other products and services we think you might like.  
If you agree, Our Company will share your data with our partner companies so that they may  
offer you their products and services.

 **What are cookies?**  
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and  
visitor behaviour information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you  
automatically through cookies or similar technology.  
For further information, visit allaboutcookies.org.  
How do we use cookies?  
Our Company uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website,  
including:  
• Keeping you signed in  
• Understanding how you use our website

 **What types of cookies do we use?**  
There are a number of different types of cookies, however, our website uses:  
• Functionality - Our Company uses these cookies so that we recognize you on our  
website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what  
language you prefer and the location you are in. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies  
are used.  
• Advertising - Our Company uses these cookies to collect information about your visit to  
our website, the content you viewed, the links you followed and information about your  
browser, device, and your IP address. Our Company sometimes shares some limited  
aspects of this data with third parties for advertising purposes. We may also share online  
data collected through cookies with our advertising partners. This means that when you  
visit another website, you may be shown advertising based on your browsing patterns on  
our website.

 **Privacy policies of other websites**  
Our Company website contains links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to  
our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.  
Changes to our privacy policy  
Our Company keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web  
page. This privacy policy was last updated on 9 January 2019.  
How to contact us  
If you have any questions about Our Company's privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you  
would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.  
Email us at: info [at] goalsarena.com

How to contact the appropriate authority  
Should you wish to report a complaint or if you feel that Our Company has not addressed your  
concern in a satisfactory manner, you may contact the Information Commissioner's Office.  
Email: info [at] goalsarena.com
